Long ago, when I was
taking part in a pickup party...
Во времена моего нубства, я играл с рандомами…
Is one healer going to be enough?
Хил, засуппортишь в одно рыло?
We'll be fine.
Всё пучком.
In fact, I didn't think we'd be fine.
Не нагнули бы нас рачком…
And sure enough,
her heal rate couldn't keep up,
ИЧСХ, одного хиллера нам не хватило.
and we suffered a party wipe.
Нагнули всех без исключения.
Isana-san kept apologizing,
but she really wasn't the one to blame.
Конечно все стали гнать на суппорта, но Исана-сан старалась как могла.
I should have spoken up that it
was going to be hard at the outset.
Было очевидно, что нас ожидает фейл, но понадеялись на авось.
I inwardly prayed that she wouldn't
get fed up with the game and quit.
Тогда я про себя пожелал, что она после этого не рейджквитнент из игры.
So then, a few months later,
she was there in another pickup party.
И вот, пару месяцев спустя, мы оказались вместе в другой пати из рандомов.
Isana-san was like...
Исану-сан спросили:
Is one healer going to be enough?
Хил, засуппортишь в одно рыло?
I'll be fine.
Всё пучком.
But with what happened before,
this time, I made sure to say something.
Но, памятуя о прошлом, в этот раз я решил вмешаться.
This will be hard with just one healer,
Раз у нас всего один хиллер,
so let's be careful not to
be too big a burden on her.
давайте не будем отвлекаться на курочку.
And then, Isana-san said one
word to me in private chat...
После чего Исана скромно кинула мне в личку такие слова…
Thanks.
Спс.
So what you're saying is,
you're bragging on your old girlfriend.
Бахвалишься, что чатился с какой-то тянкой?
How do you get that out of it?!
Разве в этом суть истории?
Am I wrong?
Разве нет?
What I'm trying to say
Суть в том, что
is that some people have trouble
asking for help when they need it.
есть люди, которые не просят о помощи, даже когда нуждаются в ней.
Ako, you understand that, right?
Ако, рубишь фишку?
Yes, I do.
Да, рублю.
I think that when someone is
feeling like they're overburdened,
И если кто-то оказался в неудобной ситуации,
it takes some compassion to
realize that and help them out.
то правильным будет по возможности помочь этому человеку.
Yes, you're right.
Ну допустим.
Very good. Now, you
understand how I feel, right?
Умница. Значит, ты готова
войти в моё положение?
Huh?
Вут?
Summer vacation will be over soon,
and school will be starting again.
Летние каникулы на исходе, и скоро начнуться школьные будни.
Can I get you to tell everyone
around us that we're not married,
Что если ты перестанешь втирать окрущающим, будто мы супруги,
but just in a regular relationship, please?
а не просто пара влюблённых?
There you go again, Rusian!
What a silly thing to say!
Опять двадцать пять, Русиян!
Не п&3#и глупости!
--Such a jokester! Oh, Rusian...
--It's actually a pretty earnest request.
— Ты такой смищной! Петрусиян…
— Мои намерения чисты.
"LV. 10: I thought we would do
our best at the culture festival?"
[Думал, сделаешь всё возможное на школьной ярмарке?]
Somebody, sell me a heat resistance potion.
Кто-нибудь, бафните фаер резист.
It really is hot, huh?
Пичот как в подмышке дьявола.
Yeah, it is. Hey, Takasaki, you got tan.
Вот-вот. Такасаки, ты теперь мулат.
Yeah, and Nishimura,
you're as pasty white as ever.
Ога, а ты всё такой же бледный, как приведение.
Yeah, well...
Ну а хули?..
Nishimura...
Нисимура…
Come with me for a minute.
Подь сюды за ударом.
Um... Segawa-san...?
Эм… Сегава-сан…?
Just come on, already!
Встань и иди!
Hey! My neck...!
Ай! Насилуют!
--My neck...! My neck...!
--Seeing Nishimura get strangled by Segawa,
— Насилуют!.. Насилуют!..
— То чувство, когда Сегава омочикаерит Нисимуру.
it sure does feel like school
has started up again, huh?
Как будто и не бывало летних каникул.
Yep.
Угумс.
Hey, you! Just because we
haven't seen each other in a while...
Твинтейланутая! Неужели ты так по мне соскучилась?..
We just saw each other yesterday, in the game.
Нонсенс! Вчера же виделись, в игре.
Yeah, but still... Is something bothering you?
Какбэ да, но… Тебя что-то беспокоит?
Ugh, why can't we just skip over the whole
"forced conversations with classmates" event
Эх, снова начался душный эвент
«встреча однокашников после летних каникул».
that comes at the end of summer vacation?
Чому нельзя просто скипнуть эту дрочь?
It's usually only suckware games
that have unskippable events, right?
Сейчас бы не давать проматывать ролики… в 2016.
Is that what you were thinking?
Mod will fix it.
For that matter,
И вообще,
how did I pull off being a regular
high school girl for all of 1st term?
как я умудрялась терпеть это весь первый триместр?
To be honest, I don't really remember much.
Честно говоря, всё как в тумане.
It's your character class, right?
У тебя биполярочка.
Ah, Akane, good morning!
О, Акане, приветики!
What are you two up to out here? An affair?
Чего это вы тут делаете? Флиртуете?
If Ako heard that, she'd withdraw again,
so please don't say that.
Ако может услышать, так что оставь свои предположения, пожалуйста.
We were just chatting, that's all.
Мы просто вышли поговорить.
You could just get along
regularly in the classroom,
Вместо того чтобы тащиться сюда,
without having to come all the way out here.
могли бы нормально и в классе поговорить.
Butt out, will you?
Завали хлебало.
It's none of your business,
you teamkilling summoner!
Тебе вообще какое дело, горе-суммонер?
You can say so after you've abandoned
your pet Mu-tan out in the mountains.
Когда ты уже наконец отнесешь
Му-тана в горы и там оставишь?
You mean in the game?!
That's mean! Mu-tan is such a good boy!
В ЛегЭйдж?
За что? Му-тан хорошо себя ведёт!
What did he ever do wrong?
Чем он тебе не угодил?
--He runs around out of control...
--Wait up!
— Без контроля он теряется в данже…
— К ноге!
--Mm-hmm.
--Mu-tan, bad!
— О да.
— Му-тан, нельзя!
And goes around pulling enemies.
А потом паровозит толпу мобов.
Yeah, yeah.
Вот-вот.
"Mu-tan, bad!" doesn't cut it!
«Му-тан, нельзя!» мой зад!
You two are both mean!
Да ну вас в озеро!
Come to think of it, Ako isn't here, huh?
Кстати, ты Ако сегодня ещё не встречал?
Yeah, you're right.
Никак нет.
I'd like to at least mess with her,
to make me feel better.
А ведь так хотелось её потраллить с утра пораньше.
"Tamaki Ako"
[Тамако Ако]
Ah, speak of the devil. It's Ako.
О, легка на помине. Ако на связи.
Hello? Rusian?
Алло? Русиян?
Good morning. Why isn't
everyone logged in today?
Доброе утро. Ты не знаешь, почему сегодня никого нет в сети?
Are you serious?
Ты сурьёзно?
Huh?
В смысле?
Good morning, everyone.
Приветствую, школота.
I am Student Council President Goshoin.
Президент студсовета — Госёин.
I know that over this long summer vacation,
Полагаю за время летних каникул, каждый из вас
everyone probably had a
productive and memorable time.
провёл время с пользой и получил массу впечатлений.
I hope that during this new school term,
Надеюсь, что в новом триместре…
--I-I'm late.
--you will continue to spend
your time productively.
— Опоздала…
— …вы с новыми силами возьметесь за учёбу.
Aww... Rusian...
Хнык… Русиян…
Nice going. Way to overcome
the desire to stay home and skip.
Молодцом. Не пошла на поводу у желания остаться дома и загнуть школу.
Well, Rusian, you said you
wanted to see my face, after all.
Дак ведь, Русиян, ты сказал, что хочешь увидеть меня во плоти.
Maybe I'll go home, instead.
А вот мне вдруг домой захотелось.
Okay, everyone,
Так, ребятки,
it's the start of the longest term of the year!
начался самый длинный триместр в году!
Let's get ourselves fired up!
Зададим-ка жару!
Ah... It's so cool...
Ах… Прохладненько…
Oh, yeah...
Охеренно…
Ah, I missed you, my little War Machine.
Ах, как же я скучала, моя адская машина.
Say, how much of your lost gear
did you manage to get back?
Слышь, какую часть эквипа ты уже успел восстановить?
Hmm, let's see, 20 percent, maybe?
Хмм, процентов двадцать, наверное…
You've still got a long way to go.
Надо бы как-то ускориться.
Um, Rusian, since you're
reassembling your gear anyway,
Эм, Русиян, сдаётся мне, что в этот раз, пока ты гриндишь шмот заново,
you're trying to get something
a little better than before, aren't you?
ты пробуешь подобрать что-то с лучшими статами.
Huh? Is that what you're doing?!
Что? Так вот чем ты занимаешься?
I hate it when girls are as intuitive as you.
За это я и не люблю проницательных девушек.
Hey, Nishimura!
Нисимура, ты офонарел?
Hold on, hold on, hear me out!
Погодь-погодь, ты послушай!
You know how after you make your gear,
you sometimes get buyer's remorse?
Бывает же, что собёрешь сет, а потом сожалеешь о созданном билде.
You wish your enchants
had gone a different way,
Можно наложить другие энчанты на эквип,
or that for the same price, you'd have
bought the other one, instead?
или купить другую пуху по той же цене.
I'm talking minor-change-level stuff...
А ещё можно вложиться в другие статы…
What you had before was fine,
so buy it again, and be of some use!
Прошлый билд был норм. Хорош раковать, собирай старый шмот!
R-Right!
Будет сделано!
Okay...
Дык вот…
Everyone, when you hear
"2nd term," what do you think?
Котаны, с чем у вас ассоциируется «второй триместр»?
Huh? Distributing the rewards
from the summer events.
Э? Сортировка плюшек за летние эвенты?
Pumpkin collecting during the Halloween event.
Фарминг тыквенных голов во время Хэллоуина?
Surveying the marketplace to prepare
for the large-scale fall update.
Исследование рынка в предверии мажорного осеннего обновления.
The Christmas event with Rusian!
Рождество наедине с Русияном!
That's not what I me-own!
I'm talking about school, not the game!
Нихреня! Я не про игры спрашиваю, а про школу!
Is there something going on?
Скорее бы домой свалить.
"Saki"
[Са]
"ko"
[ки]
"sai"
[фест]
"Sakikosai"
[Сакифест]
When you think of September,
Сентябрь жи, а значит
you think of Maegasaki High's
culture festival, Sakikosai, right?
в Маегасаки будет проводится школьная ярмарка — Сакифест.
Oh...
Вон оно чё…
Hey, guys, this is the culture festival.
Э, слышь: «Народная ярмарка блджад».
Shouldn't you typically be
getting more worked up?
Не пора ли подорвать задницы со стулов?
Are you sure you're all high school students?
Тоже мне, школьники, называются.
Well, while it may be a nuisance,
we can't very well ignore it, either.
Это, конечно, всё прискорбно, но мы не можем просто забить на этот эвент.
Nuisance...?
Просто забить…
Since our club does have activities,
we have to participate.
Раз уж мы тут изображаем клубную деятельность, нам придётся участвовать.
Yeah, but still, what are we supposed to do?
Так-то оно так, и чего замутим?
"Show off the results of
our club" is the go-to answer.
Думаю, можно организовать выставку достижений нашего клуба.
Results? Do we have any?
Достижений? Типа ачивок в стиме?
Ako came to school.
Ако начала ходить в школу.
Достижение разблокированно
Ако начала ходить в школу
:3c
--Ta-da!
--That's it.
— Ать-оп!
— Кстати, да.
Okay, we'll put Ako on display.
Ако будет нашим трофеем.
"Celebrating School Attendance"
[Каминг-аут по-хиккански]
You don't mean as an exhibit! No way!
Вы меня на обзор выставите?
I couldn't stand exposure so unorthodox!
Не хочу быть экспонатом!
--Please don't look at me!
--Net game players fear the word "dox."
— Я не атеншнвхора!
— Есть ли жизнь после деанона?
Well, kidding aside,
Харе стебаться,
we just need to come up with
some result and present it, don't we?
нам ведь нужно показать, что мы тут не просто в игрушки играем?
Some result?
А что ещё?
If you have no ideas...
Короче, Склифосовский…
ШЛЁП
"Siege warfare"
[Осада крепости]
...then I have a proposal!
…тут такая тема нарисовалась!
Siege warfare?
Осада крепости?
You mean, the recent PvP update?
В смысле новый ПвП-режим?
Mm-hmm! The long-awaited new
content released in LA the other day,
У-му! С последним апдейтом в LA наконец-то добавили годноты.
siege warfare! What if we make
the victor of that our result?
«Осада крепости». Затащим режим, тогда будет чем похвастаться.
Yeah, but Master, siege warfare, is, you know...
Погодь, Лидер. «Осада крепости» — это же…
…глобальное ПвП-сражение на уровне гильдий, проходящее раз в неделю.
...the large-scale guild-on-guild,
player-vs-player battle held once per week.
That's what we're going to do?
И мы будем в нём участвовать?
Mm-hmm. All of us club members
will compete as one.
У-му. Тогда каждый внесёт свою лепту в дело победы.
It's perfect, isn't it?
То, что доктор прописал.
Well, yeah, I guess.
Красиво стелишь.
And if we win at this, how do we
present it for the culture festival?
Но даже если мы преуспеем,
как об этом рассказать на ярмарке?
The victors of siege warfare
become the castle lords for the week.
Осаждённая крепость на неделю становится собственностью победителя.
The guild's emblem is hoisted
boldly over the castle.
А флаг с эмблемой гильдии гордо реет над ней.
Do we even have an emblem?
Разве у нас есть эмблема?
"Student Handbook
Maegasaki High School"
[Военный билет]
[Старшая школа Маегасаки]
Um, are you saying we make
our school crest our emblem
Эм, предлагаешь, сделать герб школы нашей эмблемой
and raise that?
и водрузить его?
That's right! And we all take a
commemorative photo in front of it!
В точку! А потом наделаем нотариально заверенных скриншотов
Then we use that picture as our display panel!
и сфотошопим коллажик для экспозиции!
Siege warfare, huh?
Осада крепости?
Hmm... I'm not too wild about this.
Хм… не нравится мне эта затея.
You don't like PvP fighting?
Потому что сливаешься в ПвП?
I can't win, after all.
Меня всегда нагибают.
You seem pretty happy, considering.
Ты, похоже, к этому привыкла.
I may not like that there's a new term
and I have to go to school,
Конечно, паршиво, что нужно снова ходить в школу,
but I am happy that I get to walk
home every day with you, Rusian.
но мне приятно, что после занятий мы можем побыть вместе, Русиян.
O-Oh.
Вот как.
Come to think of it,
Ах да,
what is your class doing
for the culture festival, Ako?
что твой класс готовит на школьную ярмарку?
Um... presenting establishments near
the school who sell delicious food.
Ну… будем рассказывать о точках, где можно нажраться в окрестностях школы.
That sounds like a lot of fun.
Креатив так и прёт.
Sure, I guess.
Мопед не мой.
Don't stand around needlessly
looking tense--start fighting!
Сколько можно играть в гляделки?
Дуэлиться будем или нет?
Mm... I can't hit Rusian for no reason.
Эм…  Не могу я ни за что ударить Русияна.
You know why! This is PvP practice!
Это же тренировочный ПвП-бой!
Staring into each other's eyes
like a couple isn't practicing.
А вы развели тут шуры-муры посреди сражения.
We were not! My attack power
can't take Ako out in one shot,
Ничего подобного! Мне статов не хватит, чтобы вынести Ако с удара,
so I was planning to whittle her down
first with some reflect damage.
поэтому я жду атаки, чтобы законтрить её.
Okay, okay. Go on, get to it, Ako.
Да-да. Ако, настало твоё время.
R-Right. Well...
Ок. Ну тогда…
Ako!
Ако!
Are you all right?!
Нигде не болит?
That damage came back on me.
Часть урона вернулась мне.
Heal yourself, right away.
Сразу же юзай хил.
Right. Thank you very much.
Офк. Спасибо за совет.
For crying out loud, Ako...
Ох уж эта Ако…
No, no, Rusian...
Русиян…
Oh, Ako...
Ако…
That's enough! You're facing my bad self!
Ну всё! Ща батя вам покажет!
Extra Damage!
Over9000!
Ho, not bad, you two. With one combo,
she's already red-gauging.
Охщи, неплохо сыграно. Ещё бы чуть-чуть и ей хана.
What was that? Kind of strong, wasn't it?
Что это было? Вы не перестарались?
Sorry, force of habit.
Сорян, наигранная схема.
After a stun, Rusian always
tells me to cast Extra Damage.
Русиян придрочил меня бафать ему дамаг после стана.
Even so, that was too strong
for a shield stun, wasn't it?
Имба. Вас понерфить не нужно?
Well, stun moves are
pretty powerful, to be sure,
Конечно комбинации со станом довольно мощные,
but once I use one, I can't
use it again for a little while.
но их нельзя часто применять из-за высокого кд.
But as a result, you've switched me on.
Требую продолжения банкета.
All right, Schew, now it's my turn to face you.
Тогда, Шу, давай-ка мы с тобой сразимся.
Here goes. Fight me, Master!
Ладно. Я готова, Лидер!
Feast your eyes...
Узри же…
...on my grand magic!
…величайшую магию!
That's Master's finishing move!
Лидер кастует ульт!
She's leading off with the big guns!
Не разменивается по мелочам!
Meteor!
Метеор!
Did you think I would leap
into such an obvious AoE skill?
Ты ведь не думала, что я просто подставлюсь под АоЕ-атаку.
Wha--? You weren't in the attack range?
Как? Ты ушла из зоны поражения?
That's crazy! Monsters always are!
ЧЗХ? Обычно монстры…
My bad self is not a mob!
Батя тебе не моб какой!
W-Wait!
С-стой!
Impossible... How could I...?
ЧЗХ?… Это вообще законно?
I'll resurrect you, okay?
Ща мы вас воскресим.
You're next, Rusian! Bring it on!
Так, Русиян! Твоя очередь!
W-Wait! I can't move!
Эй! Не могу…
Impossible...
Да ЧЗХ-то?
I'll resurrect you, okay?
Ща мы вас воскресим…
Okay then, Ako!
Ладно, Ако!
Let's see if you can withstand my meteor!
Как тебе понравится мой метеор?
I'm dead for sure!
Ну вот и всё!
No, Ako, just relax and fire off an SS.
Эй, Ако, соберись и кидай SS.
R-Right.
Без базара.
Skill Sealing!
Master!
Лидер!
Brace yourself!
Ну держись!
I'll resurrect you.
Ща мы вас…
Why? Why, when my attack and defense power
Как же так? У меня статы на атаку и защиту
is so overwhelmingly higher
than the rest of you?
вкачаны под крышечку и тем не менее…
Well, in Schew's melee
fighter role, she's our PvP ace.
Ну, Шу — милишник, поэтому она вне конкуренции.
If a magic user goes one-on-one
against her, they'll usually lose.
При схватке с магом один на один, победа будет за ней.
As the tank, I have
specialized stun lock attacks.
Танк навроде меня сделает ставку на стан противника.
And Ako...
Ако же…
Her stats are pretty evenly distributed,
Её статы распределены без перекосов,
so she's more than suited for PvP play.
так что её билд больше подходит для ПвП.
That's not what my intention was.
Хотя у меня и в мыслях не было.
Master, a magic user like yourself
shouldn't be dueling to begin with.
But I've watched a few videos
where magic users like me
wiped the floor with their
opponents singlehandedly!
PvP play takes its own kind
of equipment and fighting style.
So then what, Rusian? Are you
saying that we're just a collection
of broken-down characters,
poorly suited for taking on others, is that it?
Mm-hmm.
I wasn't expecting this.
I've checked into it, and my
Apricot is not suited to PvP.
It would be quicker to start
a new character from scratch.
I tried sparring against some friends
who have done some PvP'ing,
and got my clock cleaned.
I'm fairly suited to PvP play, in my own right,
but I don't have the equipment anymore.
How many siege battles are there
before the culture festival?
They're held every Sunday,
so there are three more of them.
It's not possible, is it?
Well, worst case, we change
our culture festival presentation.
Like, say, a net game discussion panel.
I will not be there that day!
As the student council president,
I can't stick around, either.
I'm fine with just staying here
and gaming with Rusian.
No, we should get out and look around.
Well, let's do as much as we can, anyway.
Everyone get your gear in shape,
and we'll join in at the next siege battle!
This will be the Alley Cats' first campaign.
And we're starting off with the
Templar Fortress of Ray Sword.
The current owners of the castle
are a guild that goes by "The Cleaning Crew."
Are they thumbing their noses?!
It sounds cute, like a group of maids.
No... They're holding the fort,
so they're sure to be tough.
That's correct. If we take them too lightly,
they will indeed mop us up
like so much garbage.
Siege warfare will now commence.
Everyone ready? Be not
too eager, nor too timid.
Charge!
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
It looks like another guild is going first.
All right, let's watch them,
and study how they fight.
That many of them, wiped out
in less than ten seconds?
What do we do?
Let's go back!
No, we won't know how bad it is
unless we actually go through it.
--Charge!
--I don't want to!
There are no death penalties in siege warfare.
Let's try it again!
I don't want to go there anymore!
I-I'm sorry! It was an accident!
What's the big idea?!
Hey, you, that's my wife!
You want a fight? You've got one!
Hold on! We're outnumbered!
So that's it. There's a single enemy,
but our side is not one monolithic block.
All the attackers are rivals to each other.
This really will be impossible.
Apparently, to break up a deadlock like this,
we can gather together materials
and build siege weapons.
Ho? We can bust down the walls and charge in?
Mm-hmm. For example,
a giant catapult, or "gi" for short,
can be controlled by five players.
That's no good.
Wait, don't give up just yet.
Oh, what, you know the victory conditions?
Master...
I'm going to use the premium items
that you have forbidden me from using!
Under these circumstances,
there's no other choice!
No, Master! You can't use
premium items in siege warfare!
That's ridiculous!
A Drop of Yggdrasil is about the only
non-premium means of total recovery.
I've never even used such a precious item.
Just one of them runs more than 10 megas.
Selling it at the bazaar and upgrading
your equips would be more practical.
I can't accept this.
This could be a good opportunity
to wean Master off of
premium items, couldn't it?
That's true.
Is that...
Proud warriors of the elite guard, hear me!
We have but one goal--
to present that fortress to
our goddess, Nekohime-sama!
Wait up, everyone!
I never asked you to do this!
Sensei's guild is pretty strong, aren't they?
Nekohime's Elite Guard seems to be
a collection of experts at the game.
Hey, they occupied the fortress.
They sure did.
Mm-hmm.
Why don't we go now?
Afterward, though Nekohime's
Elite Guard put up a good fight,
they were beaten by a larger guild,
and chased off the lord's throne.
Our all for Nekohime-sama.
Our goddess.
The holy angel Nekohime-sama.
We devote ourselves to Nekohime-sama.
Ugh, it's not like that!
I was just chit-chatting about taking the castle,
and before I mew it, it was happening!
"History of Maegasaki High School"
Listen up, everyone.
No wholesale copying the sources.
Rearrange the sentences a little.
Roger that!
It's okay to trace the map
of the school, though.
The sources come from books
in the library and web articles.
Isn't that a bit too skimpy?
Then again, the finished materials
should end up at a pretty high level.
Right, which is why it's
so hard to get too angry.
Rusian, it's hard being the teacher meow.
Enough to turn you into
Nekohime in the classroom?
No way on earth!
Ako?
It's our class presentation.
An exhibit of Maegasaki's tasty foods, right?
That has been changed.
It was suggested that as long
as we were presenting food,
why not make it something
that could actually be eaten?
Sounds like an improvement.
Then they started suggesting
taking in money, making a profit,
and while they were at it,
to have the girls serve the guests.
Now it's starting to stray.
Right. Then they said if they did a café,
it could be a maid café.
That's way off course!
The problem is what comes next!
People just started saying,
"Tamaki-san knows about maids."
"Then she'll be the head maid!"
They put me in charge of this.
Well, I can see why they'd say that.
There's a perception among regular
people that "otaku" equals "maid."
But they're wrong!
I am a housewife, not a maid!
You're not even a housewife, right?
Besides which, they asked
me to get the uniforms,
draw up shifts, come up with serving manuals,
and a bunch of other things.
That is a pain, huh?
Well, as far as the maid uniforms,
you could work something out
with Master, couldn't you?
I suppose I could.
Well, good luck with that.
We'll help wherever possible.
Okay...
"Sette-tan, logging in!"
Stale!
I just learned about it yesterday.
W-What are you doing here, Nanako?
Y-Yeah, why is she here?
I invited her. We need as
many allies as we can get now.
As such, I ordered extra machines
for Sette and Miss Saito.
Listen, Nanako, you don't have to
take the trouble to help with this.
Oh? It sounds like fun,
you know. I'll do my best.
Yeah, but on a Sunday, too?
Why can't you direct that enthusiasm
toward the class exhibit?
Mm, sorry, Mu-tan.
You have to stay behind this time.
It's too much trouble having you
nipping at everyone and his brother.
Now, as for our strategy...
Today, we're going after the fort
of Cantor, the smallest one there is.
The guild occupying it is also small--
"Emperor Sword." They're made up
of about twenty players.
Huh? But there are only six of us.
That's a pretty steep disparity in numbers.
We'll all be killed again.
Not to worry. I have a plan.
Do you have a trick up your sleeve?
Mm-hmm. For this one time,
I have arranged for the reinforcement...
...of the server's top-class
powerhouse mercenaries, Wallenstein.
Not Wallenstein!
I knew she'd solve it with money.
Are they famous?
Yeah.
"I thought we could win
by delegating to others?"
[Думал, победишь, загребая жар чужими руками?]
Please, don't die, Master!
Лидер, не умирай!
If you die here, what do we do
about the culture festival?
На кого ты оставишь школьную ярмарку?
If we survive this, we'll win the siege battle!
Переживём это и выиграем осаду!
Next time: "The Death of Apricot."
Далее: «Конец Априкота».
Netoge Standby!
Продолжение следует!